[{"questionText":"monetize synergistic supply-chains","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":1,"author":"Evanne Cockitt","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"engineer enterprise platforms","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":2,"author":"Star Hriinchenko","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"harness 24/7 e-business","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":3,"author":"Shalom Gadney","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"streamline cross-media e-business","correctAnswers":"Technology","reward":4,"author":"Devlen Prestige","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"synergize distributed users","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":5,"author":"Jacinthe Ollenbuttel","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"implement intuitive ROI","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":6,"author":"Whittaker Roglieri","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"expedite synergistic communities","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":7,"author":"Jesus Bachnic","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"incentivize real-time bandwidth","correctAnswers":"Consumer Durables","reward":8,"author":"Sanderson Camilleri","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"redefine virtual vortals","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":9,"author":"Carson Nowland","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"envisioneer distributed deliverables","correctAnswers":"Basic Industries","reward":10,"author":"Kathy Semarke","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"enhance e-business infomediaries","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":11,"author":"Berkie Sherebrook","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"mesh turn-key e-services","correctAnswers":"Transportation","reward":12,"author":"Eolanda Bolin","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"integrate B2B e-tailers","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":13,"author":"Erina Mayman","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"reintermediate robust content","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":14,"author":"Alix Barnett","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"deploy killer functionalities","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":15,"author":"Merrick Drage","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"morph interactive e-commerce","correctAnswers":"Basic Industries","reward":16,"author":"Even Paice","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"e-enable front-end e-commerce","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":17,"author":"Claretta Gentiry","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"extend customized e-business","correctAnswers":"Basic Industries","reward":18,"author":"Mart Wellwood","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"productize extensible supply-chains","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":19,"author":"Wendel Frayne","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"repurpose killer initiatives","correctAnswers":"Miscellaneous","reward":20,"author":"Audie Wyre","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"deliver cross-platform metrics","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":21,"author":"Brit Souster","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"incentivize synergistic partnerships","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":22,"author":"Laverna Ovens","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"extend B2B portals","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":23,"author":"Constantina Denial","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"streamline holistic functionalities","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":24,"author":"Bobina Connal","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"embrace leading-edge metrics","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":25,"author":"Idette Reddings","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"incentivize innovative portals","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":26,"author":"Bianca Champley","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"mesh holistic markets","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":27,"author":"Armando Maydway","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"exploit enterprise mindshare","correctAnswers":"Transportation","reward":28,"author":"Ailina Lomasney","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"architect seamless e-commerce","correctAnswers":"Basic Industries","reward":29,"author":"Frannie Craghead","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"seize best-of-breed models","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":30,"author":"Allis Cockland","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"synthesize value-added initiatives","correctAnswers":"Public Utilities","reward":31,"author":"Kingsley Spier","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"incentivize front-end applications","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":32,"author":"Sandor Gottelier","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"deliver transparent interfaces","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":33,"author":"Jess Carnalan","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"empower global relationships","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":34,"author":"Rici Fellenor","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"utilize vertical e-markets","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":35,"author":"Alyssa Kiellor","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"cultivate cross-media e-markets","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":36,"author":"Dehlia Cayzer","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"iterate cross-media content","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":37,"author":"Bobbe Ziemens","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"extend proactive schemas","correctAnswers":"Technology","reward":38,"author":"Udall Abrashkov","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"cultivate best-of-breed ROI","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":39,"author":"Solomon Jirka","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"disintermediate end-to-end models","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":40,"author":"Antonina Ellum","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"monetize global schemas","correctAnswers":"Energy","reward":41,"author":"Karoline Siley","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"architect cross-media web services","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":42,"author":"Allene Fenlon","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"optimize next-generation niches","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":43,"author":"Kearney Killik","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"harness revolutionary web-readiness","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":44,"author":"Veronique Machans","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"streamline 24/7 infrastructures","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":45,"author":"Fanya Ervine","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"transition frictionless markets","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":46,"author":"Danyelle Pennoni","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"unleash extensible portals","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":47,"author":"Ashely Kurten","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"syndicate killer mindshare","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":48,"author":"Zebedee Kubelka","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"engineer B2C deliverables","correctAnswers":"Consumer Durables","reward":49,"author":"Kurt Huggill","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"utilize out-of-the-box relationships","correctAnswers":"Transportation","reward":50,"author":"Maryanne Bozworth","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"whiteboard customized e-business","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":51,"author":"Cassie Mottley","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"cultivate enterprise convergence","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":52,"author":"Philipa Fenton","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"expedite bricks-and-clicks infrastructures","correctAnswers":"Technology","reward":53,"author":"Cacilie Jaine","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"morph customized e-business","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":54,"author":"Jaclin Aynold","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"enhance dot-com e-services","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":55,"author":"Duffie Harget","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"morph e-business networks","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":56,"author":"Orlan Chasmor","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"integrate plug-and-play e-commerce","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":57,"author":"Randolph Millwall","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"whiteboard turn-key vortals","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":58,"author":"Cy Tellenbrook","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"leverage vertical methodologies","correctAnswers":"Public Utilities","reward":59,"author":"Starla Pomphrey","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"architect viral e-commerce","correctAnswers":"Consumer Non-Durables","reward":60,"author":"Whitaker Kordova","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"integrate robust markets","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":61,"author":"Gay Lillecrap","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"recontextualize seamless technologies","correctAnswers":"Technology","reward":62,"author":"Carol Panchin","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"incubate wireless architectures","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":63,"author":"Quentin Balmadier","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"target extensible mindshare","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":64,"author":"Bria Senior","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"morph compelling partnerships","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":65,"author":"Ceil Forestall","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"evolve integrated applications","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":66,"author":"Kimberlee Stokes","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"incubate B2B infomediaries","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":67,"author":"Denny Snufflebottom","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"scale interactive deliverables","correctAnswers":"Technology","reward":68,"author":"Norene Gollop","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"incentivize front-end models","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":69,"author":"Felic Chastney","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"monetize seamless networks","correctAnswers":"Public Utilities","reward":70,"author":"Ashely Titheridge","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"streamline 24/7 web services","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":71,"author":"Carlyle Aslett","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"enable dot-com interfaces","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":72,"author":"Ulysses Banbrook","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"implement killer networks","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":73,"author":"Janette Vobes","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"synthesize dynamic supply-chains","correctAnswers":"Energy","reward":74,"author":"Marla McDell","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"envisioneer viral paradigms","correctAnswers":"Basic Industries","reward":75,"author":"Irene Franzettoini","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"engineer scalable content","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":76,"author":"Lane McGill","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"incentivize proactive ROI","correctAnswers":"Consumer Durables","reward":77,"author":"Adda Cavy","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"syndicate virtual web services","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":78,"author":"Willis Bagenal","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"expedite cross-platform e-markets","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":79,"author":"Fedora Gonoude","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"exploit virtual web-readiness","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":80,"author":"Noak Heibl","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"whiteboard dot-com experiences","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":81,"author":"Berte Cattonnet","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"revolutionize B2C markets","correctAnswers":"Technology","reward":82,"author":"Dill Fike","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"evolve synergistic content","correctAnswers":"Transportation","reward":83,"author":"Ondrea Terzo","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"generate value-added platforms","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":84,"author":"Elladine Zealy","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"syndicate impactful portals","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":85,"author":"Lonnie Wetwood","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"visualize value-added methodologies","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":86,"author":"Dorothy Draco","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"reinvent seamless infrastructures","correctAnswers":"Consumer Services","reward":87,"author":"Cornelius Mowsdill","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Chemistry"}]},
  {"questionText":"morph bleeding-edge schemas","correctAnswers":"Capital Goods","reward":88,"author":"Jeanelle Sorrie","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"reintermediate sticky content","correctAnswers":"Finance","reward":89,"author":"Tiler Hargroves","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"implement visionary architectures","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":90,"author":"Shamus Claige","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"integrate 24/7 applications","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":91,"author":"Garnette Birrel","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"}]},
  {"questionText":"utilize bleeding-edge models","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":92,"author":"Inesita Keyzman","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"evolve open-source communities","correctAnswers":"Energy","reward":93,"author":"Skell Sabben","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"envisioneer killer e-markets","correctAnswers":"Energy","reward":94,"author":"Allyce Cristofano","topics":[{"topicName":"History"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"engineer extensible e-commerce","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":95,"author":"Melisent Jezzard","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"empower granular platforms","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":96,"author":"Mufi Cajkler","topics":[{"topicName":"History"}]},
  {"questionText":"extend dot-com e-commerce","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":97,"author":"Eleanore Vevers","topics":[{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"harness one-to-one web-readiness","correctAnswers":"n/a","reward":98,"author":"Jolene Embleton","topics":[{"topicName":"Art"},{"topicName":"Geography"}]},
  {"questionText":"e-enable turn-key technologies","correctAnswers":"Consumer Non-Durables","reward":99,"author":"Konrad Pandie","topics":[{"topicName":"Geography"},{"topicName":"Art"}]},
  {"questionText":"unleash value-added ROI","correctAnswers":"Health Care","reward":100,"author":"Hervey Humerstone","topics":[{"topicName":"Chemistry"},{"topicName":"Sport"},{"topicName":"Art"}]}]